# Hilary Sheaffer

### Elementary/Early Childhood Educator

### Contact

12029 Chaparral Drive, Bridgeton, MO 63044 636-866-9584 hiljoyloh@gmail.com

Dr. Henry St. Pierre Assistant Superintendent Fort Zumwalt School District 555 E. Terra Lane O'Fallon, MO 63366

### Dear Dr. Henry St. Pierre,

As someone who enjoys learning, I have made it my career to encourage others to enjoy it as well. I am currently looking for the school I can call "home" for the next 5+ years and I am hoping to find that in your district.

I graduated from Lindenwood University in 2016 with my Bachelor's in Elementary Education and since then I have had a wide variety of experiences all over the St. Louis area.

My journey through the education field began as a student teacher in the Lindbergh School District and has brought me to my current position in the Hazelwood School District as a 2<sup>nd</sup> grade teacher.

I would love to meet with you in order to answer any questions you have about the experiences between 2016 and today. I am positive that I would make a great addition to your team and community. I look forward to meeting with you!

Sincerely,

Hilary J. Sheaffer

## HILARY

### **SHEAFFER**





### **OBJECTIVE**

To accept a position as an Elementary teacher in a school district that is well known for providing the best learning experiences for their students and their educators as well.



#### **EDUCATION**

**Bachelor's Degree in Elementary Education | Lindenwood University** AUGUST 2011 – MAY 2015

**Certification in Early Childhood Education** FEBRUARY 2017

**Substitute Certification** FEBRUARY 2015



### **EXPERIENCE**

First and Second Grade Teacher (Title I school) | Hazelwood School District JULY 2019 – PRESENT

**Substitute | Parkway, Rockwood, and Orchard Farms School Districts** AUGUST 2017 – MAY 2018

**Student Teacher | Lindbergh School District**JANUARY 2015 – APRIL 2015



#### **MISSION**

AS SOMEONE WITH A LOVE FOR LEARNING, I HAVE MADE IT MY CAREER TO ENCOURAGE CHILDREN TO LOVE LEARNING AS WELL AND REACH THEIR HIGHEST POTENTIAL.